Hi, I'm Kathleen.
大家好 我叫凯萨琳
I lead the careers team at UDACITY.
在优达学城由我带领我们的职业团队
We support students in their job search.
我们为学生们寻找工作提供支持
The careers team knows what employers
are looking for in a job candidate.
我们的团队了解每个求职者都在寻找什么
And we want to work with you to market
yourself as the best person for the job.
我们想和你一起努力 把你以最佳人选的身份推销出去
Whether it's a new role or
a promotion at your current company.
无论是新角色，还是在当前公司的晋升
You need to be proactive in your career
development to be job ready at graduate.
在你的职业生涯中 你需要在毕业时做好积极的准备工作
For this reason,
正是因为如此
career services are available
throughout your nano degree experience.
在你的纳米学位经历中 职业服务将能够帮助到你
It's important to remember, while you're
here to learn the technical skills for
要记住 在这里学习工作技能是重要的
a job, it's equally important to know
how to communicate those skills to
同样的 知道如何将这些技能通过一个应用
an employer, through an application,
your online profiles, and in interviews.
在线资料 面试 展现给雇主同等重要
Let's meet the careers team who
will be with you along the way.
让我们来认识一下将会一路陪伴你们的职业团队
>> Hi, I'm Rachel.
大家好 我叫雷切尔
Along with a network of career
mentors our team is here to help
与一个职业指导网络一起 我们的团队
you from when you begin to look for
jobs until you accept your job offer.
将会在你的求职过程中全程提供帮助
Career support is present at different
stages throughout your nano degree and
纵观整个纳米学位 职业支持会有所不同
we encourage you to go through
all of them regardless of where
我们鼓励你去仔细检查
you are in your job search.
在寻求工作中所忽略的地方
The first of these career
services are the projects in
这些职业服务中 首要服务便是
the Career Development
section of your classroom.
课堂中的职业发展部分
UDACITY career services include guides,
lessons and
优达学城的职业服务包括指导、课程
personalized feedback on topics
like talking to recruiters,
比如与招聘人员所谈论话题的个性化反馈
interviewing and
optimizing your online profiles.
面试和在线资料优化
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[无声音]
>> And I'm Trin.
我叫特林
In order to graduate career-ready,
为了完成职业生涯的准备工作
you should continuously work
on your career development.
你应该在你的职业发展中继续工作
Like with all learning, beginning
something earlier means you are more
就像所有的学习一样，开始的越早
prepared when it's time
to apply that learning.
意味着当你应用所学时 你会有更充足的准备
When your dream job pops up
you want to be ready for it.
你梦想的工作突然冒出来的时候 你已经游刃有余
We'll support you throughout your
career development, on the forums,
我们自始至终都将支持你的职业发展 包括以讲坛
in career coach appointments, and
through the Career Resource Center.
预约职业教练 职业资源中心 的形式
>> Hi, I'm Kirsten and
I head up employer relations at UDACITY.
大家好 我叫柯尔斯顿 我是优达学城的人事主管
Once you've completed the curriculum,
you'll be ready to apply to jobs and
一旦你完成了课程，意味着你准备将所学的技能应用到工作
talk with employers.
以及与雇主的交谈中
UDACITY partners with industry-leading
companies who are looking to hire
优达学城合作伙伴拥有行业领先的合作公司
skilled and passionate people, like you.
这些公司希望招聘到技艺精湛激情昂扬的人 比如你
Having hiring partners means
you'll have direct and
拥有招聘伙伴意味着我们能够直接 优先的将你
preferential exposure
at these companies.
推荐给这些公司
This will help give you a leg up in your
job search as you explore your career
当你在探索职业选择中寻求工作和
options, and
develop a career path unique to you.
发展自己独特的职业道路时 这将让你占尽优势
After you create your first
core nano degree projects,
在你创建第一个核心纳米学位项目之后
you'll then be prompted to begin
your career development with us.
将会提示你和我们一起开始你的职业发展
>> We'll then be there
with you from then on.
我们自始至终与你同在
As you explore your career options and
pursue your dream role.
当你探索你的职业选择和追求梦想的角色时
We look forward to working with you.
我们期待和你一起努力。
[MUSIC]
[音乐]